[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "The date of the wedding, can I tell him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "I mean were you even remotely surprised at the verdict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, I feared for the worst and hoped for the best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "How would you summarize her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I think the best way to summarize her is to parrot the testimony that was actually given in the trial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Are you -- are you a mother, Dorothy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dorothy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "But can you honestly imagine anybody that you knew who's a mother ever behaving like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, I think the key word that you just said is rational.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Is that what you personally believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I believe that this was an accident that snowballed out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Are you concerned about her ability to lead a free life in relative safety?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I am concerned for her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Do you want to clarify it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, I went into the case, I was asked to come and donate my time for free, to work on this case, to work on the science aspect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, I think before you determine someone is a risk, you have to take the time to understand them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "I mean, have you ever heard of or been involved with any case like this in your life where a mother has not reported a child missing for over 30 days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, the responses that I've gotten back from the people that have experienced trauma, actually, there were several responses that talked about situations where they pretended the individual in their life had not really died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "You can confirm you're alive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "I'm alive, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Twain", "Mark Twain"]}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Was it a bit disconcerting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "My response was, you know, it happened to Mark Twain so I simply quoted Mark Twain's comment that rumors of his demise were exaggerated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, you know, that is the number one question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "I mean, what do you say to the skeptics who said this was never ever had a chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I think that's a very valid question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "When was the exact moment you knew that she was not going to go through with the wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, the previous weekend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "When did you find out that she was doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "On Sunday night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "I mean do you think that she took you for a ride?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I think an argument could be made that she took me for a ride.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Has she got any money out of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Yes, but not as much as she would have if she'd married me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "I mean how much has she walked away with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, she asked for a Bentley right before we split.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "How much was the ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "The ring was -- I'm not sure exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "On top?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "A little but not a great deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What is your -- you're a smart guy, what does your gut instinct tell you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "That there's more that we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Have you ever had your heart broken before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Is he heartbroken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I mean, he's OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Were you very saddened by what happened personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, I was stunned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Did you shed a tear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Yes, I shed a couple of tears.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Have you spoken to her since?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Oh, yes, I've seen her several times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "One that you believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I think that there -- you know, I think -- I think the explanation probably has more to do with the fact that, you know, did it run its course and she didn't really love me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "But have you thought of trying somebody nearer your own age, Hef, in their 30s or something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Well, one of the two girls I'm seeing now is 27.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hef"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Do you feel -- do you feel conned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "To some extent, obviously, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "And is that -- is that even vaguely humiliating for someone like you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "No, it's not humiliating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "It would have been worse if she'd waited to get married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anna"]}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Who are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, Anna has been -- she is -- was going to be our maid of honor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "And she's on the left or right there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "She's on the -- our left.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Emotionally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shera"]}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Who's the other young lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "The other is Shera.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "So am I right in thinking that you have replaced Crystal with two proper new girlfriends now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "EFNER: Yes, that is correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "So, I mean, how sorry should people be feeling for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Not too sorry, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "You've bounced back strongly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I am in better shape than I would have been if I'd been married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Has the experience, to be serious for a moment, has it put you off ever getting married again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "They were clearly no fans of hers, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "The girls are very, very protective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "That Crystal had ulterior motives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I think so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Who is the other guy that you obliquely referred to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I really don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Would it really anger you if you discovered she was seeing somebody behind your back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I am prepared for that probability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "You think that's what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I think that is part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I would say the great difference is that one thing, any girl who's ever been with me can say, quite frankly, is that I never played shady.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Any comment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "Yes, well, my first wife was a brunette.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "And what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "And she cheated on me right before we got married.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Why has America got itself into this hole,, do you think, financially?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "Well, if I knew the answer to that one, I'd be much wiser than I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "When you put your finger on the business model of America, incorporated, what are the problems?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "We didn't pay as we went.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Has America got to go and do business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I think it's the wrong attitude.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you think America should go back to being a manufacturing country at its heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Yes and entrepreneurial.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Less consumer-led and more production?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RBR", "JJ", "CC", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "Well, production where it works, and entrepreneurial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Lost a bit of the entrepreneurial zeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "EFNER: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Do you trust Obama to get it right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I did to begin with.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "Made me very sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Do you believe that could ever happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "I find much of the circumstances very suspect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "Would you ever countenance offering a \"Playboy\" cover to somebody like Casey Anthony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "It is amazing the number of people that have Tweeted me immediately afterward, asking whether or not we would do a pictorial on her, et cetera.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miss America", "Miss America"]}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Even though you would know, instinctively, it would sell millions of copies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "There are classic examples, as a matter of fact, historically in terms of a black Miss America that we didn't do a pictorial on, because she was a black Miss America and I knew that would hurt her, and other similar examples.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Is it just your instinct tells you that it would be inappropriate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Well, I don't think it's entirely subjective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I have mixed feelings about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110714pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Presumably, it's all about glamour and sex and fun of your old club, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]